

## About me

I'm a healthcare product manager with a medical degree and 20+ years of software development experience. I excel in building trust based collaboration with key opinion leaders, academic partners and financial stakeholders, while having meaningful conversation with the engineering teams. I'm looking for opportunities in Austria, ideally in

healthcare IT or innovation management to leverage on my domain knowledge in medical, healthcare areas as well as on my software development experience.

## **Employment history**

5+ years at GE Healthcare, 5+ years at Wolters Kluwer, 10 years as a researcher and freelance software developer.

## Senior Product Manager, GE Healthcare

June 2020 - present

- Definition and execution of product strategy and roadmap
- Engagement with internal and external stakeholders
- Collaboration with engineers, product managers, product designers, and data scientists, as well as key stakeholders and executives

## Consortium Research Leader, GE Healthcare

Oct 2015 - June 2020

- Led collaborative research activities with academic and clinical partners, startups across Europe
- Identified external funding opportunities
- Developed grant proposals for EIT Health, H2020 and national funds, pitched grant proposals to funding bodies

# **Business Unit Manager**, Wolters Kluwer Hungary Oct 2011 - Oct 2015

- Developed the natural sciences and medical portfolio of the publishing house
- Organized conferences, managed 30+ subscription or open access journals, published books
- Built the network of editors-in-chief and editorial board members with respected academicians, clinicians
- Led the editorial, sales and advertising team (10 people)

Medical portal editor, Wolters Kluwer Hungary, Oct 2010 - Oct 2011

### **Software developer**, Startup, *Nov 2000 - Oct 2010*

■ Founded a software company to develop software solutions for research groups, universities and private companies

## **Achievements**

■ Developed the product strategy of a healthcare data aggregation and interoperability platform service in 7 months, which enables internal

#### Technical skills

- Agile software development, Scaled Agile Framework (SAFE)
- Healthcare interoperability (HL7, FHIR, Fast Healthcare Interoperability Resources)
- Microsoft Office, Rally, JIRA, Confluence, Git, GitHub
- Programming languages (Python, Javascript, SQL)

### Soft skills

- Friendly and authentic demeanor
- Problem solving
- Stakeholder engagement
- Business acumen
- Innovation management
- Presentation and communication skills
- Mentoring internal team members or startups

## Language skills

- Fluent English communication
- Native Hungarian
- Basic German

## **Education and training**

- Executive MBA, Budapest University of Technology and Economics, 2018-present
- Medical Doctor, Semmelweis University, Faculty of Medicine, 1994-2000

### **Hobbies and interests**

Running

- and external software teams to collect patient and device data from different sources (e.g. EMR, RIS) and formats (HL7, FHIR, DICOM) on-premise or in the cloud.
- Actively engaged with 3 pillars of EIT Health ecosystem (innovation, acceleration, education). Involved GE Healthcare in 25+ projects with 60+ partners, obtained 3 million EUR from external funding.
- Executed & successfully closed a 16 million USD national R&D grant with 3 partners in Hungary about next generation software platform development in healthcare (multi-disciplinary team meeting for oncology therapy planning, artificial intelligence framework)
- Initiated the HelloAl training programme about potential usage of artificial intelligence in healthcare for university students and later for healthcare professionals. In the first 2 years during face-to-face courses we trained 120 students. During the COVID-19 pandemic we quickly transformed the training to online format, expanded the outreach and trained 800 participants across Europe about the technical, ethical, medical and commercial aspects of Al.

 Electronics projects, tinkering, microcontrollers